<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>Chamar Boy</title><link href="https://chamarboy.com/" rel="alternate"></link><link href="https://chamarboy.com/feeds/all.atom.xml" rel="self"></link><id>https://chamarboy.com/</id><updated>2021-04-18T05:34:02+05:30</updated><subtitle>An insight into SC/ST life</subtitle><entry><title>The college experiance</title><link href="https://chamarboy.com/the-college-experiance.html" rel="alternate"></link><published>2021-03-01T22:57:00+05:30</published><updated>2021-04-18T05:34:02+05:30</updated><author><name>Chamar Boy</name></author><id>tag:chamarboy.com,2021-03-01:/the-college-experiance.html</id><summary type="html">&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You people have nothing to worry about, you'll get jobs easily. The
problem is for people like us&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Ankur quipped while we are discussing the prospects of getting job after
college.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;W&lt;/em&gt;e are discussing the prospects of getting job after college. The
uncertainty caused by past IT recessions trigger …&lt;/p&gt;</summary><content type="html">&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You people have nothing to worry about, you'll get jobs easily. The
problem is for people like us&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Ankur quipped while we are discussing the prospects of getting job after
college.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;W&lt;/em&gt;e are discussing the prospects of getting job after college. The
uncertainty caused by past IT recessions trigger this. Weather is
pleasant. We are sitting outside a &lt;em&gt;Nirulas’&lt;/em&gt; under picnic umbrellas.
This is part of a laid back market complex which does not do much
business. It is walking distance from college, we love to take a long
walk from college to here.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Ashish has been kicked out from the group, and some friends choose to
stay with him. I wanted to, but I choose to stay where Anusha seems to
be comfortable. This has reduced the number from around 15 to 5. We are
bunking some class, sitting outside a food joint. I am holding Anusha's
hand, she might have felt my hand twitch.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Being a perennial back bencher and flunking in numerous examinations
(total 5 papers till now), I do not know how to respond to this
unexpected attack. Being a SC/ST student, it has become apparent to me
that I cannot be just lazy, average or not interested, I am just an
incompetent loser who does not deserve to sit between these enlightened
beings. They seem to be doing me a favor by caring to listen to me.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;After a long silence, considering the path of least resistance, i
decided to change the topic.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The job market is difficult after the recession. All of us have some
hard time ahead of us&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;But the Jack Maa look alike had to make make his point.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Why do you why people like you would look into the private job market?
There's so many of amazing opportunities available in the government
sector. And believe me, you will earn far more than the private sector&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Oh, somebody say something…...silence!!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It's not for everyone to see things your way.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I think that ended the discussion.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Oh, the crucial part of this open discrimination practiced by teachers,
students and even chaprasis of this great institute – &lt;em&gt;Bharati
Vidyapeeth&lt;/em&gt;, Delhi and the even greater dumb-ass university it
represents – Guru Gobind Singh Indraprastha University, was allocating
the roll numbers – I think first 6 roll numbers represent the reserved
community – SC/STs or &lt;em&gt;chuda/chamar&lt;/em&gt; as thought of by the these
enlightened and entitled middle class chutias.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I looked at Anusha as she is looking into my eyes. She is asking me to
ignore this, but I cant seem to decide. We decide to go back to college.
She has been one of those rare humans who has offered me parity – of
thought, ability….respect of being treated like another human being.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We were happy gang of 15 middle class misfits, who who liked each other
some of them had romantic inclinations. Some things have changed. Now we
are 5/7 people (2 of them cant seem to decide).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Anusha is like a friend I never deserved or worked for. Of all the
people in my life, I think she is the only one who feels what I am going
through. I have never shared details of the legal and moral issues I am
facing at home, but she only knows about Gunjan, and how I am still
deeply in love with a with her.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I feel i am selfishly using her. I have no prospects, a loser to the
core, still she prefers me. Even I don't prefer myself these days. She
still does.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Gunjan....I don't know if she will be back or she has gone for good. I
cant stop thinking about her. Maybe she is dating a stud she
deserves...maybe she is being tricked by one of the thousand bastards
who seem to be following her day and night. Anyways, I don't seem to
deserve her. She has a good idea or some suspicion of me being an
undeserving chamar who tricked her into accepting my proposal.....good
that nothing happened....this guilt of tricking her would have killed
me.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Here is Anusha, the best of girls I would ever meet....holding my hand
despite knowing my reality. I can feel love when she holds my hand.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;And I don't know how it happened. I don't even remember the first time I
held her hand, it seemed to have happened spontaneously.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As far as i can remember, she was talking me about a guy she seemed to
have been dating, and it did not end well...i understood....and maybe
that is how we became friends.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Much of the things between us seemed to be unsaid. She will wait for me,
I would wait for her....find any simple excuse to be with her.....go on
long walks....bunk classes to be with her. She did not seem to mind
sitting on my old scooter.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She somehow understood....and I could feel her....her hands told me all
i needed to know....some weird telepathy shit....or i am delusional.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I know what hurts her, I know when I hurt her, and how could I make it
alright. She never hurt me.....and when she did....it was brutal&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Coming back to the present moment,This awkward argument means Jack Maa
is targeting me now. After kicking Ashish and his loyalists out,
everyone in this leftover group of 7 is a bloody beta, all ugly, short
or severely limited in intellect....basically an un-date-able set of
severely undeserving poor specimen of the male form. No one Anusha or
any conscious female or any functional girl would ever consider.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Or am I about to be proved wrong???&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;</content><category term="Story"></category><category term="College"></category><category term="Caste"></category><category term="India"></category><category term="Delhi"></category><category term="Engineering"></category><category term="Friends"></category><category term="Gunjan"></category><category term="JackMaa"></category></entry><entry><title>2003 - the year that changed everything</title><link href="https://chamarboy.com/2003-the-year-that-changed-everything.html" rel="alternate"></link><published>2020-09-26T22:57:00+05:30</published><updated>2021-04-18T05:34:01+05:30</updated><author><name>Chamar Boy</name></author><id>tag:chamarboy.com,2020-09-26:/2003-the-year-that-changed-everything.html</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;26 Sept 2003&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I think i passed engineering. Not happy but relieved.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I am oscillating between a deep sense of regret of not doing the things
I wanted to do in engineering and the relief that I survived despite all
odds.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As part of the first batch of engineering from …&lt;/p&gt;</summary><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;26 Sept 2003&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I think i passed engineering. Not happy but relieved.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I am oscillating between a deep sense of regret of not doing the things
I wanted to do in engineering and the relief that I survived despite all
odds.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As part of the first batch of engineering from this college, there are
not many prospects to start with. Though I am trying for jobs, my heart
knows that i will not get any - grades and the way I looked - deformed
bald and itchy.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I am trying to prepare for GATE, to finally do the nerdy stuff which i
am very capable of doing. 4 years of engineering taught me a valuable
lesson - people are highly ordinary - not capable of creating anything
new, just masters of mugging and following the orders.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The legal storm caused by my sisters adventures finally seems to be
over, my father seems to have it handled. I never disclosed it to
anyone, but I am prepared to do &lt;em&gt;anything&lt;/em&gt; if the situation goes worse.
Every night I evaluate the strategy, the tools and the things I need to
be careful about. This decision is a combined result of my current
state, my duties as a brother and my complete belief that life would not
be any different from what I have experienced it till now. Life in
prison sounded way real and acceptable than spending years with the
scared yet competitive sheep of engineering college graduates.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;My mom and father love each other. I cant make sense of it. My father is
a principled, hard working individual, though my mother is really
nothing but manipulative, power hungry, ugly excuse of a female. It is
not like only I hated her, all of us did, except my father.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;At least once a month, my mother and father would take off to a &lt;em&gt;date&lt;/em&gt;
of sorts - they would leave in morning and come back late at night. This
has been one of the happiest days of the month for me and my sisters for
years.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Off late, I have distanced myself from my second sister. I like being
alone and destructive, a man who has no one and nothing to loose. The
people around me are too busy to cater to their plans to take over the
world, who would care about a discolored, bottom of the class chamar
boy? Hey, my answer is the same as you, hence the going out in brotherly
glory plan.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I am happy at the prospect of never going back to the college again,
forced to communicate with those judgmental pricks of classmates,
teachers who would congratulate me and suggest that i would get a fat
&lt;em&gt;sarkari&lt;/em&gt; job now. Somehow Infy, TCS, Polaris etc are never discussed
with me.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Mom and Dad left for their monthly date, sister is out doing whatever
she does. I am up, go to the computer room and dial up the Internet.
Checking mail, yeah....no prospects, the self destruct plan stands.
Phone rings.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I hate phone....she never calls, and she wont. She knows now, at-least
suspects it...me being a chamaar. How can the shiniest, most popular
girl date a chamar? Anyways, I will explain the situation later.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I answer, the digits seem similar - the call is from our family cell
phone. I pick up, though i do not recognize the voice. The voice is of
my uncle, he is trying to tell me something important in a very non
important way. The car has broken down, and i need to come to get it
fixed. I should get a friend to drive my bike back so I could drive the
car after getting it repaired. The location is near a hospital. I say
yes, and did not argue how illogical the plan sounded. In the background
i could hear a lot of commotion. Anyways, i needed to patch up my
appearance and drive a bike with no rear brakes for 100 kms. When you
are on a death wish, these choices are really not a choice.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I call up a friend, a fellow SC/ST boy who flunked and now is a junior.
Caste seems to be the only quality which defines my life right now. I am
afraid of the general friends - ex girl friend might have blabbered..the
news might have spread....and i have lost my looks. Most of people avoid
me in college, the friends i thought i had left me because a girl who
seems to have loved me, told everyone that i molested her. I never did.
I literally and figuratively had lost my face and most friends with it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;SC friend shows up. He is riding pillion and i am driving my Bajaj
caliber chroma. My friend is asking a lot of questions, i don't have any
answers.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I drive, having some non-sense chatter with friend. My mind is racing
though. Maybe my grandmother is sick or died and maybe my dad is too
broken up to drive. This seemed to be the most logical interpretations
of the facts i could recall.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;After an hours drive, we arrive at a hospital. As i enter, I could see
100s of faces I had forgotten. They seemed to be all watching me
closely. I am not sure if its due to my current appearance or due to the
incident.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Something is amiss. The damn car seems fine. People are crying, I am
trying to find someone talk-able. Someone directs me to a sub group.
Mother is crying, trying to be sad than she is.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Father is dead.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;How, why and what the fuck? Did her stupidity killed him or was it an
assault? I am enraged, hoping it was an assault....and i get to kill
someone for it...finally justify my existence. It was a heart attack.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I don't understand...are they sure? This is a good private
hospital...they must be sure. I could have reacted way more naturally
had I was not surrounded by literally 100s of people. Indians love
drama, and i was customary bound to provide it today.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Something has hardened me enough to disobey conventions, and to realize
what it means.....I am no longer the kid brother, or someone who can ask
for help. With my stupid mom and uncontrollable sister.....what the
literal fuck?? I need help to come to terms of what is happening to me
and now this added responsibility too?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Nothing is fair. As my brain is processing the implications, I am
interrupted - there are choices to be made. Where to do the &lt;em&gt;kriyas&lt;/em&gt;? I
don't know. I am thinking here. I have my uncles, and I do not know what
is to be done. My mother interferes. She turns off her crying for a
moment and tells me to tell them Rohini, at our new home. I want to
protest, but then a dollop of emotional superiority infused cold logic
shrewd logic is disclosed....we need to keep up the reputation. I just
want to be alone, as soon as possible. I say yes. Handing over the keys
of the bike to the friend i tell him to be careful, the rear brakes are
not working, the front ones do, but they are more effective than one
anticipates.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Life would never be the same again.&lt;/p&gt;</content><category term="Story"></category><category term="Start"></category><category term="India"></category><category term="death"></category></entry><entry><title>Why now ??</title><link href="https://chamarboy.com/why-now.html" rel="alternate"></link><published>2020-09-26T22:57:00+05:30</published><updated>2021-04-18T05:34:02+05:30</updated><author><name>Chamar Boy</name></author><id>tag:chamarboy.com,2020-09-26:/why-now.html</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;I did not knew that the issue of caste discrimination is widespread in
the world, let alone India.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Recently an ignorant asshole of general garbage origin shared an article
which kind of forced me to increase the priority of this rather dead
blog.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.zdnet.com/article/commentary-how-indias-ancient-caste-system-is-ruining-lives-in-silicon-valley/"&gt;How India's ancient caste system is ruining …&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;</summary><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;I did not knew that the issue of caste discrimination is widespread in
the world, let alone India.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Recently an ignorant asshole of general garbage origin shared an article
which kind of forced me to increase the priority of this rather dead
blog.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.zdnet.com/article/commentary-how-indias-ancient-caste-system-is-ruining-lives-in-silicon-valley/"&gt;How India's ancient caste system is ruining lives in Silicon
Valley&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.washingtonpost.com/opinions/2020/07/13/new-lawsuit-shines-light-caste-discrimination-us-around-world/"&gt;WashingtonPost : A new lawsuit shines a light on caste discrimination
in the U.S. and around the
world&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://thewire.in/caste/cisco-caste-discrimination-silicon-valley-dalit-prejudice"&gt;The Cisco Case Could Expose Rampant Prejudice Against Dalits in
Silicon
Valley&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For the uninitiated, &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Chamar&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; is one of the sub castes, which also
comes under rather lager or politically correct term &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Dalit&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Though centuries have passed, the discrimination remains prevalent as
ever.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Most people generally assume that people belonging to this category of
caste have an easy, express path to professional success and prosperity,
A notion which i aim to challenge and provide a real life view.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I can only cover the aspects which i have faced in the most objective
manner, to provide an unbiased perspective.&lt;/p&gt;</content><category term="Story"></category><category term="Why now"></category><category term="What"></category><category term="Caste"></category><category term="India"></category></entry><entry><title>A letter to Anusha</title><link href="https://chamarboy.com/a-letter-to-anusha.html" rel="alternate"></link><published>2020-09-01T22:57:00+05:30</published><updated>2021-04-18T05:34:01+05:30</updated><author><name>Chamar Boy</name></author><id>tag:chamarboy.com,2020-09-01:/a-letter-to-anusha.html</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;I loved you. Something in me still loves and misses you.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;My long due closure.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Anusha, of all the females i have known in my life, you were the most
kind, affectionate, intelligent and million other good things.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You were flawless.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I really wanted to be good for you....for …&lt;/p&gt;</summary><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;I loved you. Something in me still loves and misses you.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;My long due closure.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Anusha, of all the females i have known in my life, you were the most
kind, affectionate, intelligent and million other good things.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You were flawless.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I really wanted to be good for you....for the fact that i could not
imagine not having your voice in my life.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As you had given hundreds of hours of me whining about my ex girlfriend
Gunjan, I wanted to be sure.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For me, you were pure....an angel....maybe a god.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I really wanted to be sure, when i commit to you I commit for good, not
as a insecure rebound from Gunjan.......you were the nicest.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;And that time never arrived, and i was sure that it may never. I have
not ever really gotten over Gunjan...and i really knew that you have
bigger things in store for you....to me it seemed like you chose to
score low....your potential was infinite....and I am a chamar boy
....getting Rs 20 a week, who just wanted to die.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;And it got worse....skin gave away....and so did my belief of me being
destined for self destruction.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I did misbehave with you and probably cheated you emotionally.....but
you have to understand....you were the only good in my life back then.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I never really blamed for what happened next...i knew i deserved
it....but i would have heard it from you.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It may be possible yet improbable that you might carry some guilt of
what happened. Hope this helps....i deserved it and i am sorry.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I still miss you....for you are the only person who may still understand
me.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For me, you are still the only person who is truly broken me.....it
feels like you still have a part of me, and i still have yours. I still
feel you...i still understand your emotions your hands your breath and
those thousand different emotions your beautiful eyes conveyed.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I still imagine me exhaling on you soft skin and feeling your scent.&lt;/p&gt;</content><category term="Story"></category><category term="Anusha"></category><category term="College"></category><category term="Now"></category><category term="Missing you"></category><category term="India"></category></entry><entry><title>Introduction</title><link href="https://chamarboy.com/introduction.html" rel="alternate"></link><published>2020-09-01T22:57:00+05:30</published><updated>2021-04-18T05:34:01+05:30</updated><author><name>Chamar Boy</name></author><id>tag:chamarboy.com,2020-09-01:/introduction.html</id><summary type="html">&lt;h1&gt;Who&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I am a Chamar boy, born in a somewhat normal middle class (not Chamar
middle class, normal middle class) family.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I was born in 1981 in a semi-urban village in Delhi.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;My father had a Bajaj Super in 1990, and we got a landline telephone in
1997.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I know …&lt;/p&gt;</summary><content type="html">&lt;h1&gt;Who&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I am a Chamar boy, born in a somewhat normal middle class (not Chamar
middle class, normal middle class) family.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I was born in 1981 in a semi-urban village in Delhi.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;My father had a Bajaj Super in 1990, and we got a landline telephone in
1997.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I know it's hard to imagine a village in Delhi now, but in 1990 till the
time we stayed there, it had a water well, we had cows and cow dung was
the primary fuel though my father got us LPG ever since i can remember.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So now here we are. Year is 2020, the most chaotic year for my
generation, but somehow I am better placed than I ever was.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I have a spacious (in most senses) house, 2 cars, 2 dogs, a beautiful
and intelligent son and mostly loving wife.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;And I work at Facebook.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;That is the big reveal. 2 Cr.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;That declaration is not an achievement, I just want my readers to know
what they are dealing with here.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This Facebook and the money thing seems important to society.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Apparently it kind of justifies my existence. People are nicer.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hypocrisy of society becomes very apparent when you are even minutely
successful.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Ever since I have realized what Chamar is, and how apparently we have
special powers given by the constitution, a subject of envy and
inflammatory debates on social media and hushed discussion in social
circles.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1&gt;Why&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As I am getting older, I do tend to think about the past, mostly to
learn from it. I remember those days, when my self worth was negative
million.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I was targeted, gaslit at college, did not take it well, slipped in a
depression, developed Psoriasis, spent years in a sham ayurvedic ashram
with skin swollen like a balloon filled with pus covered in cow dung.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Abandonment by the girl I loved, the girl who loved me, friends, my own
family. A failed suicide attempt, living through vengeance, death of
father, a sister which destroyed the family, destroyed my existence.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;All because I am a Chamar.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It was not all bad, It somehow made me realize the strengths which I
thought I never had, and did generally well. Something kept me pushing,
and I kept breathing.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I want to share my journey with you. Anyone who feels like I did in my
Chamar years can get some semblance of hope or direction and hopefully
he/she does not commit the grave mistakes I did, or felt like how I
felt.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;To Readers&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I hope you get a balanced view of a Chamar life and hopefully next time
you feel like feeling taller, maybe you will be empathetic to the SC/ST
humanoid in your class, office or school.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you feel like saying stuff, you have the full freedom to give me a
piece of your mind, absolutely brutally.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I have will update the blog in a way that anonymous are welcome and give
me their best shot. It's sort of a fuel to me now.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;To my fellow Chamaar/SC/ST Readers&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I hope you learn.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I hope you feel hopeful.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I hope you can believe in yourself, rather than what society is telling
you silently.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If my journey can benefit any one of you, my efforts would make sense to
me.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1&gt;How&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I will try to narrate it in a novel kind of style.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You already know where I am.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Logically my story starts in class 11, when I started realizing the
implications of being a chamar, what it meant for career, for making
friends, girls and neighborhood.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I have changed certain key details, to preserve the identity of the
people involved.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I will narrate the journey, leaving the judgment to readers.&lt;/p&gt;</content><category term="Story"></category><category term="Introduction"></category><category term="Why"></category><category term="What"></category><category term="Casteism"></category><category term="India"></category></entry><entry><title>College Year 1 ends</title><link href="https://chamarboy.com/college-year-1-ends.html" rel="alternate"></link><published>2000-06-01T22:57:00+05:30</published><updated>2021-04-18T05:34:01+05:30</updated><author><name>Chamar Boy</name></author><id>tag:chamarboy.com,2000-06-01:/college-year-1-ends.html</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;Loser….in every sense of the word.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Gunjan has left, I dont exactly know why….but I do have few ideas. I do
not have the courage to face her. If she knows that am a chamar boy,
then she has decided this, then things might be better left unsaid …&lt;/p&gt;</summary><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Loser….in every sense of the word.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Gunjan has left, I dont exactly know why….but I do have few ideas. I do
not have the courage to face her. If she knows that am a chamar boy,
then she has decided this, then things might be better left unsaid….this
is something I am born with, cant really change that….i have dreaded
this moment for last 3 years …. feel relived in a weird way.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I did decently in the first semester, the second semester was a
different story all together. A lot of things have changed. I failed an
exam, and barely passed this semester – 59% . This effectively means I
am bottom of the class, solidifying my chamar level intellect and
capabilities. I am not really concerned, there are bigger problems.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Home is a hellhole right now. I am dealing with some potentially legal
and ethical issues ...due to some questionable acts done by my younger
sister. As a brother, I am bound to act….these acts may be illegal, and
might really require physical confrontation…..decisive
confrontations….my sister’s honor is involved. The dilemma is how to
make sure she remains protected even if I am not there anymore….cant
involve parents, they are already drinking to their full capacity…. They
wont be able to take it. I am trying, but nothing seems to be do-able
without really killing anyone in a clean strike. Legal is not an option,
my sister would come out looking bad. Cant really discuss with
friends….or ask for help….cant share the details. I am on my own for
now.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Gunjan leaving me, and the manner in which she did…..leaves me with a
lot of questions….my existence, my worth and the fact that this chamar
birth is the underlying layer of my identity ….. which cannot be
changed. I cannot ignore this feeling of hollowness, and the lingering
doubt that no matter how much I try or contribute….i would be judged as
a chamar, not as a human being.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It is a depressing thought and I am not dealing with it correctly...but
what is the point? I cannot undo any of this. Does it mean that I need
to consider caste as the primary criteria to make friends? Should I
ignore natural attraction or should I be attracted to only caste
approved friends? How would 2 caste appropriate couple look like in
college ? Do I even know a female who is SC/ST? Would she spurn me as
she may not want to be seen as SC/ST? Or it would be a comic relief
moment like in old movies where the comedy sidekick would have a comedy
sidekick female as a mate? Am I a sidekick in my own story? Are all
SC/ST burden on society? Is reservation a right earned or is it a nice
offering by society’ nice ppl….the kind that white people felt when they
encountered tribal/natives in their imperial conquests? Do I really have
friends ? Would they react similarly?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I have lots of questions.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Maybe she left me because I suck….generally as a person….too tight
lipped, no fun….and have no ability to afford fun. Gunjan gets Rs50 a
day, and I get Rs 20 a week. She needs to live life at its
fullest...maybe I was becoming a roadblock in this….my being generally
negative and jealous of most guys she interacts….i know all of them are
bastards….but hot girls do prioritize feeling of jealousy rather than
analyzing the behavior in a cerebral way.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I have succeeded in inheriting a scooter from my father, but I do not
want her to be seen on it….it is way below her standards...and I am not
sure if I am the right choice for her….so better is to be alone….and
stay away...self preserve….whatever is left….and maybe some day….. The
thing I am absolutely sure of that she is better off without
me….tainting her with chamar touch is the last thing I want to do.
Gunjan, before formally telling me to stay away….also made clear that we
were never in a relationship….i can only imagine how disappointing she
must be feeling in me.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Maybe it never happened...maybe it is all in my head….and maybe this all
is true. I try not to think of this.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I am starting to like cigarettes. They dont ask any questions, dont
judge you, loyal to the core for the ones who are just checked out of
life….blaming cigarettes and not the world or their inability to deal
with it. 5 minutes of pure bliss….mind blanks out….numbness for 5
minutes….that is all I can afford right now. Not worried about
cancer….it would be a blessing in disguise right now….a perfect alibi
for my failures.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;At college….i do get a breather. Friends do know about the breakup….they
are sympathetic...and help me with studies. The only thing which I seem
to have gained is Anusha and Ashish….both of them seem to have accepted
me despite my chamar-ness.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Anusha is a popular girl in college. She talks to me mostly, happy and
optimistic….somethings which do give me hope..that these circumstances
are my and my burden alone...life can be fair and enjoyable.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It is not all bad, my account seems like a lot of self pity. There are
some things which have my attention…... I got my computer – aVintron P3
with 16MB RAM, 4 GB of HDD. That poor thing is facing the brunt of my
attention. It took some convincing with my father to make him shell out
45k for this latest computer. RAM was bit on low side, but I am making
it work.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In college, we still use the age old Turbo C, an outdated IDE which
works on DOS or windows. Most my my college mates still use it. For me
it is too old. I had computers as an elective in my school, where I
consistently topped my class without any efforts. I seem to have a knack
for computers, so I decided to kick it up a notch….try the most exciting
thing happening in computer science – LINUX.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;CDs – which came along with computer magazine were the primary medium of
getting latest software, or there was grey market for pirated software.
I have become friends with some of competitors at local video game
parlor. Taking up computers as major in college seems like a golden
ticket to all Indian middle class, hence some of these friends had the
luxury of computer magazine subs. They are kind enough to let me borrow
them. This months CD was RED HAT linux 6.2, which no one could make
sense out of. I have the complete ownership of it. So here I was….with
an exam tomo, and computer with this thing called LINUX in front of me.
Time flew – I did not give up even after rendering the computer
unusable. There is no internet – only man pages to make sense out of
this so called GUI installer. I soaked it all in...it made a whole lot
of sense to me. I failed in that exam, but it felt like a good bargain.
This has become a sole obsession for me now, whenever I font have money
(almost everyday) I spend this time breaking my head with Linux and
making sense of it. I am fascinated by the intellect of these people,
their generosity, and their confidence of putting your work out there. I
can endlessly write about Open Source and how it is the greatest feat
achieved my mankind so far. It outweighs industrial revolution, bulbs,
electricity by a long shot in my opinion. All those inventions were a
result of greed, profit or just grandiose….this was something
different….people working for a cause...with no incentive….trying to
change the world with little hope and pure merit….and they were steady
and unapologetic. And here I was, still fighting some obsolete human
construct without any rhyme or logic. In a way, this philosophy appealed
to me deeply, more than anything else in the world.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I am seeking people – teachers or students with similar outlook, but I
am hoping for too much. College or the incompetent, Chamar loathing
teachers which this college hired are the biggest reason of me giving up
on academics.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;My bitterness with this college has followed a linear graph. From a
proud and optimistic student on day 1, when I was on top of the world,
to this dismissive, pessimistic hollow creature...the decline has been
phenomenal. This instance which happened in this semester broke my last
belief of intellectual parity in this world.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In one of the tests we were given the following problem&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Q: Write a function to find number vowels in a string. (5 Marks)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;My solution was on the lines of something similar as below:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;int count_vowels(char input[])&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;{&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;int num_vowels=0;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;char character;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;for (int i=0; i&amp;lt;strlen(input), i++)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;{&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;//convert to lowercase&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;if ( input[i] &amp;gt;= A)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;character = input[i] – 32;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;else&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;character = input[i];&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;switch(character):&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;{&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;case ‘e’:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;case ‘i’:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;case ‘o’:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;num_vowels++;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;break;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;}&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;return num_vowels;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;}&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I was sure of getting 30/30. Most of the my peers did get 30/30. I got
25/30. I went to our pretty teacher. I waited for the initial excitement
to settle, then went to her with the answer book, with this solution
open.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Mam, this is correct, but marked as wrong.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Why are you not using multiple breaks? And what is this weird if else
thing in the loop.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is to handle uppercase letters.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Ok, why is not every case statement followed by break?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Mam, it is a shortcut to optimize………………..&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;How many shortcuts in life would you take?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I was not sure what she meant...or I was not sure if it was intended in
the way I perceived it. I looked up to make sure. She was slightly
smiling, with undeniable hint of superiority ….the same which expression
rich people have when they deny a request from a helpless being….dog or
beggar.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I paused, then without saying a word, I went back to my desk. I was in
denial for few days….coming to terms with a hard reality is
difficult…..given I had wonderful teachers in my school. A core
biological value of being treated fairly was in question. When the
denial progressed to acceptance, my my transformation was complete.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I have taken this as a kind of challenge….I wont give a fuck and still
pass...lets see how bad it can get?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;And it has gotten really bad. Bad to the extent that despite being the
best coder in this batch, I would never get the marks to reflect that.
Like a typical bullheaded uncaring asshole that I am, I have no desire
to raise this very prove-able discrimination, I would take whatever
marks were granted with a smile. People were given perfect 100 in labs,
and I would get 70,80 but never above that. These are the lowest marks
awarded in these lab evaluations.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I am not budging. As my tenure in this college progresses, this typical
Punjabi overconfident cunt of a teacher would not leave a single
opportunity to deny me a fair evaluation and other teachers included lab
assistants have joined in.&lt;/p&gt;</content><category term="Story"></category><category term="College"></category><category term="Family"></category><category term="Circumstances"></category><category term="Teacher"></category><category term="Harassment"></category><category term="Fair"></category><category term="Respect"></category></entry><entry><title>College Starts</title><link href="https://chamarboy.com/college-starts.html" rel="alternate"></link><published>1999-09-01T22:57:00+05:30</published><updated>2021-04-18T05:34:01+05:30</updated><author><name>Chamar Boy</name></author><id>tag:chamarboy.com,1999-09-01:/college-starts.html</id><summary type="html">&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;No more Maths!!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I am in love with my dream girl Gunjan, and she seems to love me too&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Got into a prestigious engineering college, that too on a &lt;em&gt;free
    seat&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Mom and Dad seem to be proud.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I have loyal friends who are fun and inspiring too&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Sisters are …&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;</summary><content type="html">&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;No more Maths!!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I am in love with my dream girl Gunjan, and she seems to love me too&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Got into a prestigious engineering college, that too on a &lt;em&gt;free
    seat&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Mom and Dad seem to be proud.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I have loyal friends who are fun and inspiring too&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Sisters are happy in their own worlds&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;After six months of anxiety, Everything seems to be going my way. World
is a fair place, life is fair.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Then why is my spidey sense tingling ? I should be happy, content and
optimistic.....but the tingling is growing bigger, unavoidable ,
something that demands urgency.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As I am thinking, the pessimistic chamar boy inside me gets another
opportunity to tell me to recall the lessons imparted by my father. The
mini horror stories which my father seems to hide, or sometimes he would
try to share a varnished version of his rough experiences being chamar
boy senior.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;His stories were often re-runs, though his narration and emotions would
change each time he recounted his experiences.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I tried to listen, though my sisters seemed to phase them out. I think
being older they have listened to these stories more than me, and now
they know the story but cant seem to relate the message to current
circumstances.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A father walks a difficult path, whether to fill his kids with optimism,
or to warn them about how fucked up the real world is. How men turn into
farm animals – just give them privacy and some leverage over the other
person.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is what i have gotten to know so far from my father and his choice
of composition of his re run stories.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For last 2 years, things have been bitter in the house. Ever since my
elder sister ran off to marry a brahmin boy, my father seems to have
taken a rather pessimistic view of life. His sentences indicate
dejection, sound impersonal and formal. It seemed like his faith in his
kids has been lost. Every tone sounds defensive, as if he is trying to
distance us from the decisions we may take. He became a very formal
father. There may have an attempt to acknowledge me as an adult member
of the house, which translated to more duties and expectations without
any chance of failure.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There may have been some resentment from my side too....considering i
have been physically and publicly beaten by my father on a few
occasions. Last incident was just few months back.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;I will finally get a computer!!! &lt;/em&gt;That is the gain i have focused my
attention on. I have earned it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Gunjan seems happy, we talk everyday at night...the telephone bills have
been noticed, so i call her from a public phone-booth owner by a creepy
guy. Rs 1 for 3 minutes of awkward silences, random talk. I do get
probed for lost time and begging for more pocket-money is a weekly
ritual....just to hear her voice.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Gunjan and I share a something spiritual... a level of emotional
intimacy that is hard to describe. I know she is damaged, misunderstood,
happy, having a very desirable female form which attracts all kinds of
attention.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I have not told her about my feelings for her, and she makes extra
efforts to make me feel like another extra in her life....she likes me,
waits for my call, gives me attention, tries to keep tabs on me
too...but the beauty of it all has been ....i always felt insecure...her
words express indifference though her tone is always enticing....a
riddle that i can never solve.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Elder sister visits, though her visits are very stressful.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Younger sister is not doing well though. I never identified with
her...her values, her approach to problem analysis and solutions has
been highly circumspect. Ever since my elder sister eloped, we look out
for each other, though I do not understand her choices. She is my new
support system. She is struggling with studies, personal relationships
though she seems to be happy and optimistic.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;My mother has become more viscous. She seems to be always on lookout for
anything remotely suspicious. Our college timings, friends....everything
was her area of attention and instant judgment.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Most nights, my father and mother would drink up senseless. Me and my
sister were assigned the ground floor, mother and father used to occupy
first floor. At ten, we would depart to our respective rooms. In my
estimate, my father and mother consume 3-4 pegs of whiskey along with a
beer each before losing the sense of loudness and awareness.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I could hear her inciting my father everyday on either of these few
issues:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;how their own daughter betrayed them&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;how their siblings have betrayed them&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;how my sister and i are following in our elder sisters footsteps.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Some nights, my mother would cover a few issues and on really bad ones,
they would cover all, get drunker than usual and call despicable names
for all .... including us.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;My nights were simple - trying to call Gunjan at nights, be on guard if
things go bad.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The really bad nights were the one where my mother would succeed in
finding something which was remotely true....and my sister’s struggle in
her life would give her periodic ammunition. Special night horror show
used to start with our parents discussing about my sister or me, in an
extremely loud, obnoxiously oblivious way...as if they deliberately want
us to hear their messaging, giving them benefit of doubt of being drunk.
After 25-40 minutes of this intentional yet unintentional drama, my
father would call out for &lt;strong&gt;both&lt;/strong&gt; of us. These edge of seat, awaiting
the dreaded call-out moments kept me anxious to say the least. I have to
keep listening, to be ready to defend us, if and when we would be called
out to &lt;em&gt;discuss&lt;/em&gt; issues in my chamaar family style.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;My father has 2 very noticeable flaws&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;He is and has been afraid of conflict.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;His judgment seems to be influence-able, proven by the fact that my
    illogical, viscous mom had succeeded in isolating him from the world
    he nurtured – our village where we were genuinely cared for. His own
    kids seem like a liability to him now&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;p&gt;My uncles -father’s brothers have been the best tutors to nurture us as
kids, we being the initial ones in our unusually big joint family. Our
extended family was respected and feared at the same time. My granddad
had a larger than life image – his tool was his aggression, flamboyance
and the original devil may care attitude.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;My father and uncles were an exact mirror opposite image of my
grandfather. Logical, careful, painfully aware of their status in
society’s pecking order. All of them made out of the same material as my
grandmother – a genuine diplomat with extremely caring personality –
perfectly complementary characteristics to my grandfather. My time spend
in this environment has been the most happiest, blissful period of my
life. This deserves a separate post later.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Coming back to spidey sense....it has been tingling ever since my elder
sister has eloped, every night has been a torture, a reminder of how i
need to run away from home as soon as i start earning. I have a whole
plan – i would move to a different city, elope with Gunjan and live
happily ever after and telling about my truth in the deathbed. She is
everything i need!! and sometimes she helps me distance from my fucked
up nights. Though I cannot afford love in current circumstances, I need
her…she is the only normal thing in my teenage life, my only sense of
intimacy of thought...a sense of belonging, loving.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It is 10, and horror show resumes : S03E234.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I have the luxury of space – I have taken the living room at ground
floor as my room. The room is directly above our functional living room,
where my mom and dad &lt;em&gt;discuss&lt;/em&gt; their daily challenges and defeats. I can
hear when they move their glasses or go to the balcony. I try to not be
in this room when these drunken conversations are happening. Cannot call
Gunjan right now, I might be called in anytime upstairs, then I would
have to explain her about the abrupt phone hangup. Also her phone is
rarely available from 10-11, I prefer to call her after my parents
conclude their night party.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;ChamarBoy, come upstairs….we need to discuss something.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The dreaded call has come. Why now, why today...my mind is racing. My
sister is also called. I get out...i can see my sister standing in the
hallway too. This time the issue seems to be about her
academics...though my father thinks of these meetings as a bonus to
teach me.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We try to get out of it, by making feeble excuses, but I am not sure if
those were heard. We have become somewhat used to this routine. We are
smiling outside with our minds racing.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The stairs are dark, sister (lets call her rani delusional) lits up the
dreaded U shape stairway. We start walking. As we reach in the middle to
take the U step, mom unbolts the 1&lt;sup&gt;st&lt;/sup&gt; floor entry gate.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Sab sach batana warna ghar se nikal denge tere papa….tumhe humari
life mein problem create karne ke alawa aata hi kya hai……&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;..&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;…”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Mom’s background abuses are faded away as we enter the living room. The
smell and the moment remind of your place in this house.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Shaadi karni hai ya padhai?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I looked up – It is not a question you may ask your 17 year son. I am
not sure if he asked me or my sister?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He was looking at me.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;5 seconds pass, it cant be that obvious ? Can it be?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“padhai”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Toh padhta kyun nahin hai?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“papa mein padh raha hoon”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Tera admission kitni pareshani ke baad hua hai, bhagte bhoot ki
langoti pakdi hai tune, kabhi pura kaam bhi kar liya kar”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He has a point there – I cant seem to get anything completed. I do the
bare minimum and take my chances. Too much life is happening around me.
Gunjan takes away most of my time and attention.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Papa, I am doing well now&lt;/em&gt; (I really am not)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;After a couple of more awkward questions, we are signaled to leave. It
is 12 now, new day has started.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Is Gunjan up??&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I hurry to my room and hookup a stolen/borrowed landline phone into the
telephone sockets which I have secretly extended to my room. This is a
lineman’s phone – big yellow with rotary dial. One of my friends had
gifted this phone to me – I think he stole it when lineman was up in the
pole and left his work bag on ground. What a genuine buddy!!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It is ringing………..no response…...is she angry?? Is she done with me??
Has she found someone better ( everyone is better!!)??….maybe she wants
me to feel disposable….she is a weird girl...i think she sabotages
things..when they become real…&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;No response. I decide not to try again….she might be sleeping or she is
ignoring me...either ways I cant seem to sleep.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Things with Gunjan have been complicated to say the least. A loser
general boy who couldn't not even clear BBA exams told her that I belong
to SC/ST category, hence I am able to clear the entrance exams. This is
not a false statement...it was my truth to tell….i wanted to tell her
when I was ready.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It devoids me of the privilege of telling my truth personally, and I
would have told her when I was sure of my worthiness. Yes I have been
lying to her….self preservation reasons mainly. A prom queen cannot be
seen with a chamar boy….that much was clear to me.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I could see her slipping away...she has been acting aloof...even by her
hot girl persona.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Love or even creating a possibility of love is an expensive proposition
for anyone at my standards. Even I ignore the substantial emotional
baggage and guilt I have been carrying….my world was built on a false
identity….all of which may collapse once my truth is out.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;And there are college studies too...12 exams in a curtailed
1&lt;sup&gt;st&lt;/sup&gt; semester in 4 months including my demon - Mathematics!&lt;/p&gt;</content><category term="Story"></category><category term="College"></category><category term="Family"></category><category term="Circumstances"></category></entry></feed>