<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>Chamar Boy</title><link href="https://chamarboy.com/" rel="alternate"></link><link href="https://chamarboy.com/feeds/all.atom.xml" rel="self"></link><id>https://chamarboy.com/</id><updated>2021-01-31T03:59:58+05:30</updated><subtitle>An insight into SC/ST life</subtitle><entry><title>2003 - the year that changed everything</title><link href="https://chamarboy.com/2003-the-year-that-changed-everything.html" rel="alternate"></link><published>2020-09-26T22:57:00+05:30</published><updated>2021-01-31T03:40:20+05:30</updated><author><name>Chamar Boy</name></author><id>tag:chamarboy.com,2020-09-26:/2003-the-year-that-changed-everything.html</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;26 Sept 2003&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I think i passed engineering. Not happy but relieved.
 I am oscillating between a deep sense of regret of not doing the things I wanted to do in engineering and the relief that I survived despite all odds.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As part of the first batch of engineering from …&lt;/p&gt;</summary><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;26 Sept 2003&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I think i passed engineering. Not happy but relieved.
 I am oscillating between a deep sense of regret of not doing the things I wanted to do in engineering and the relief that I survived despite all odds.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As part of the first batch of engineering from this college, there are not many prospects to start with. Though I am trying for jobs, my heart knows that i will not get any - grades and the way I looked - deformed bald and itchy.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I am trying to prepare for GATE, to finally do the nerdy stuff which i am very capable of doing. 4 years of engineering taught me a valuable lesson - people are highly ordinary - not capable of creating anything new, just masters of mugging and following the orders.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The legal storm caused by my sisters adventures finally seems to be over, my father seems to have it handled. I never disclosed it to anyone, but I am prepared to do &lt;strong&gt;anything&lt;/strong&gt; if the situation goes worse. Every night I  evaluate the strategy, the tools and the things I need to be careful about. This decision is a combined result of my current state, my duties as a brother and my complete belief that life would not be any different from what I have experienced it till now in college. Life in prison sounded way real and acceptable than spending years with the scared yet competitive sheep of engineering college graduates.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;My mom and father love each other. I cant make sense of it. My father is a principled, hard working individual, though my mother is really nothing but manipulative, power hungry, ugly excuse of a female. It is not like only I hated her, all of us did, except my father.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;At least once a month, my mother and father would take off to a &lt;em&gt;date&lt;/em&gt; of sorts - they would leave in morning and come back late at night. This has been one of the happiest days of the month for me and my sisters for years.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Off late, I have distanced myself from my second sister. I like being alone and destructive, a man who has no one and nothing to loose. The people around me are too busy to cater to their plans to take over the world, who would care about a discolored, bottom of the class chamar boy? Hey, my answer is the same as you, hence the going out in brotherly glory plan.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I am happy at the prospect of never going back to the college again, forced to communicate with those judgmental pricks of classmates, teachers who would congratulate me and suggest that i would get a fat sarkari job now. Somehow Infy and TCS etc were never discussed with me.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Mom and Dad left, sister is out doing whatever she does. I am up, go to the computer room and dial up the internet. Checking mail, yeah....no prospects, the plan stands. Phone rings. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I hate phone....she never calls, and she wont. She knows now, atleast suspects it...me being a chamaar. How can the shiniest, most popular girl date a chamar? Anyways, I will explain the situation later.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I answer, recognized the digits from our family cell phone, though i did not recognize the voice. The voice is of my uncle, he is trying to tell me something important in a very non important way. The car is broken down, and i need to come to get it fixed. I should get a friend to drive my bike back so I could drive the car after getting it repaired. The location is near a hospital. I say yes, and did not argue how illogical the plan sounded. In the background i could hear a lot of commotion. Anyways, i needed to patch up my appearance and drive a bike with no rear brakes for 100 kms. When you are on a death wish, these choices are really not a choice.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I call up a friend, a fellow SC/ST boy who flunked and now is a junior. Caste seems to be the only quality which defines my life right now. I am afraid of the general friends - My friend sort of ex girl friend might have blabbered..the news might have spread....and i have lost my looks. Most of people avoid me in college, the friends i thought i had left me because a girl who seems to have loved me, told everyone that i molested her. I never did. I literally and figuratively had lost my face and most friends with it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;SC friend shows up. He is riding pillion and i am driving my bajaj caliber chroma. My friend is asking a lot of questions, i dont have any answers.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I drive, having some non sensical chatter with friend. My mind is raching though. Maybe my grandmother is sick or died and maybe my dad is too broken up to drive. This seemed to be the most logical interpretations of the facts i could recall.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;After an hours drive, we arrive at a hospital. As i enter, I could see 100s of faces I had forgotten. They seemed to be all watching me closely. I am not sure if its due to my current appearance or due to the incident. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Something is amiss. The damm car seems fine. People are crying, I am trying to find someone talkable. Someone directs me to a sub group. Mother is crying, trying to be sad than she is. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Father is dead.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;How, why and what the fuck? Did her stupidity killed him or was it an assult? I am enraged, hoping it was an assult....and i get to kill someone for it...finally justify my existence. It was a heart attack.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I dont understand...are they sure? This is a good private hospital...they must be sure. I could have reacted way more naturally had I was not surrounded by literally 100s of people. Indians love drama, and i was customary bound to provide it today. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Something has hardened me enough to disobey conventions, and to realize what it means.....I am no longer the kid brother, or someone who can ask for help. With my stupid mom and uncontrollable sister.....what the literal fuck?? I need help to come to terms of what is happening to me and now this added responsibility too?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Nothing is fair. As my brain is processing the implications, I am interrupted - there are choices to be made. Where to do the &lt;em&gt;kriyas&lt;/em&gt;? I dont know. I am thinking here. I have my uncles, and I do not know what is to be done. My mother interferes. She turns off her crying for a moment and tells me to tell them Rohini, at our new home. I want to protest, but then a dollop of emotional superiority infused cold logic shrewd logic is disclosed....we need to keep up the reputation. I just want to be alone, as soon as possible. I say yes. Handing over the keys of the bike to the friend i tell him to be careful, the rear brakes are not working, the front ones do, but they are more effective than one anticipates.&lt;/p&gt;</content><category term="Story"></category><category term="Why now"></category><category term="What"></category><category term="Caste"></category><category term="India"></category></entry><entry><title>Why now??</title><link href="https://chamarboy.com/why-now.html" rel="alternate"></link><published>2020-09-26T22:57:00+05:30</published><updated>2021-01-27T01:58:50+05:30</updated><author><name>Chamar Boy</name></author><id>tag:chamarboy.com,2020-09-26:/why-now.html</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;I did not knew that the issue of discrimination is widespead in the world, let alone India.
Recently an ignorant asshole of general garbage origin shared an article which kind of forced me to increase the priority of this rather dead blog.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.zdnet.com/article/commentary-how-indias-ancient-caste-system-is-ruining-lives-in-silicon-valley/"&gt;Commentary: How India's ancient caste system is ruining …&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</summary><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;I did not knew that the issue of discrimination is widespead in the world, let alone India.
Recently an ignorant asshole of general garbage origin shared an article which kind of forced me to increase the priority of this rather dead blog.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.zdnet.com/article/commentary-how-indias-ancient-caste-system-is-ruining-lives-in-silicon-valley/"&gt;Commentary: How India's ancient caste system is ruining lives in Silicon Valley&lt;/a&gt;  &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.washingtonpost.com/opinions/2020/07/13/new-lawsuit-shines-light-caste-discrimination-us-around-world/"&gt;WashingtonPost : A new lawsuit shines a light on caste discrimination in the U.S. and around the world&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://thewire.in/caste/cisco-caste-discrimination-silicon-valley-dalit-prejudice"&gt;The Cisco Case Could Expose Rampant Prejudice Against Dalits in Silicon Valley&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For the uninitiated, &lt;strong&gt;Chamar&lt;/strong&gt; is one of the sub castes, which also comes under rather lager or politically correct term &lt;strong&gt;Dalit&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Though centuries have passed, the discrimination remains solid as ever.&lt;br&gt;
Most people generally assume that people belonging to this category of caste have an easy, express path to professional success and prosperity, A notion which i aim to challenge and provide a real life view.  &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I can only cover the aspects which i have faced in the most objective manner, to provide an unbiased perspective.&lt;/p&gt;</content><category term="Story"></category><category term="Why now"></category><category term="What"></category><category term="Caste"></category><category term="India"></category></entry><entry><title>Introduction</title><link href="https://chamarboy.com/introduction.html" rel="alternate"></link><published>2020-09-01T22:57:00+05:30</published><updated>2021-01-31T03:59:58+05:30</updated><author><name>Chamar Boy</name></author><id>tag:chamarboy.com,2020-09-01:/introduction.html</id><summary type="html">&lt;h1&gt;Who&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I am a Chamar boy, born in a somewhat normal middle class (not Chamar
middle class, normal middle class) family.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I was born in 1981 in a semi-urban village in Delhi.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;My father had a Bajaj Super in 1990, and we got a landline telephone in
1997.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I know …&lt;/p&gt;</summary><content type="html">&lt;h1&gt;Who&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I am a Chamar boy, born in a somewhat normal middle class (not Chamar
middle class, normal middle class) family.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I was born in 1981 in a semi-urban village in Delhi.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;My father had a Bajaj Super in 1990, and we got a landline telephone in
1997.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I know it\'s hard to imagine a village in Delhi now, but in 1990 till
the time we stayed there, it had a water well, we had cows and cow dung
was the primary fuel though my father got us LPG ever since i can
remember.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So now here we are. Year is 2020, the most chaotic year for my
generation, but somehow I am better placed than I ever was.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I have a spacious (in most senses) house, 2 cars, 2 dogs, a beautiful
and intelligent son and mostly loving wife.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;And I work at Facebook.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;That is the big reveal. 2 Cr.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;That declaration is not an achievement, I just want my readers to know
what they are dealing with here.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This Facebook and the money thing seems important to society.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Apparently it kind of justifies my existence. People are nicer.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hypocrisy of society becomes very apparent when you are even minutely
successful.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Ever since I have realized what Chamar is, and how apparently we have
special powers given by the constitution, a subject of envy and
inflammatory debates on social media and hushed discussion in social
circles.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1&gt;Why&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As I am getting older, I do tend to think about the past, mostly to
learn from it. I remember those days, when my self worth was negative
million.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I was targeted, gaslit at college, did not take it well, slipped in a
depression, developed Psoriasis, spent years in a sham ayurvedic ashram
with skin swollen like a balloon filled with pus covered in cow dung.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Abandonment by the girl I loved, the girl who loved me, friends, my own
family. A failed suicide attempt, living through vengeance, death of
father, a sister which destroyed the family, destroyed my existence.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;All because I am a Chamar.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It was not all bad, It somehow made me realize the strengths which I
thought I never had, and did generally well. Something kept me pushing,
and I kept breathing.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I want to share my journey with you. Anyone who feels like I did in my
Chamar years can get some semblance of hope or direction and hopefully
he/she does not commit the grave mistakes I did, or felt like how I
felt.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;To Readers&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I hope you get a balanced view of a Chamar life and hopefully next time
you feel like feeling taller, maybe you will be empathetic to the SC/ST
humanoid in your class, office or school.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you feel like saying stuff, you have the full freedom to give me a
piece of your mind, absolutely brutally.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I have will update the blog in a way that anonymous are welcome and give
me their best shot. It\'s sort of a fuel to me now.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;To my fellow Chamaar/SC/ST Readers&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I hope you learn.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I hope you feel hopeful.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I hope you can believe in yourself, rather than what society is telling
you silently.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If my journey can benefit any one of you, my efforts would make sense to
me.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1&gt;How&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I will try to narrate it in a novel kind of style.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You already know where I am.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Logically my story starts in class 11, when I started realizing the
implications of being a chamar, what it meant for career, for making
friends, girls and neighborhood.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I have changed certain key details, to preserve the identity of the
people involved.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I will narrate the journey, leaving the judgment to readers.&lt;/p&gt;</content><category term="Story"></category><category term="Introduction"></category><category term="Why"></category><category term="What"></category><category term="Casteism"></category><category term="India"></category></entry></feed>