<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>Chamar Boy - misc</title><link href="https://chamarboy.com/" rel="alternate"></link><link href="https://chamarboy.com/feeds/misc.atom.xml" rel="self"></link><id>https://chamarboy.com/</id><updated>2021-03-05T15:44:37+05:30</updated><subtitle>An insight into SC/ST life</subtitle><entry><title>2003 - the year that changed everything</title><link href="https://chamarboy.com/2003-the-year-that-changed-everything.html" rel="alternate"></link><published>2021-03-05T15:44:37+05:30</published><updated>2021-03-05T15:44:37+05:30</updated><author><name>Chamar Boy</name></author><id>tag:chamarboy.com,2021-03-05:/2003-the-year-that-changed-everything.html</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;Date: 2020-09-26 22:57
Category: Story
Tags:  Why now, What, Caste, India&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;26 Sept 2003&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I think i passed engineering. Not happy but relieved.
 I am oscillating between a deep sense of regret of not doing the things I wanted to do in engineering and the relief that I survived …&lt;/p&gt;</summary><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Date: 2020-09-26 22:57
Category: Story
Tags:  Why now, What, Caste, India&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;26 Sept 2003&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I think i passed engineering. Not happy but relieved.
 I am oscillating between a deep sense of regret of not doing the things I wanted to do in engineering and the relief that I survived despite all odds.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As part of the first batch of engineering from this college, there are not many prospects to start with. Though I am trying for jobs, my heart knows that i will not get any - grades and the way I looked - deformed bald and itchy.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I am trying to prepare for GATE, to finally do the nerdy stuff which i am very capable of doing. 4 years of engineering taught me a valuable lesson - people are highly ordinary - not capable of creating anything new, just masters of mugging and following the orders.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The legal storm caused by my sisters adventures finally seems to be over, my father seems to have it handled. I never disclosed it to anyone, but I am prepared to do &lt;strong&gt;anything&lt;/strong&gt; if the situation goes worse. Every night I  evaluate the strategy, the tools and the things I need to be careful about. This decision is a combined result of my current state, my duties as a brother and my complete belief that life would not be any different from what I have experienced it till now. Life in prison sounded way real and acceptable than spending years with the scared yet competitive sheep of engineering college graduates.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;My mom and father love each other. I cant make sense of it. My father is a principled, hard working individual, though my mother is really nothing but manipulative, power hungry, ugly excuse of a female. It is not like only I hated her, all of us did, except my father.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;At least once a month, my mother and father would take off to a &lt;em&gt;date&lt;/em&gt; of sorts - they would leave in morning and come back late at night. This has been one of the happiest days of the month for me and my sisters for years.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Off late, I have distanced myself from my second sister. I like being alone and destructive, a man who has no one and nothing to loose. The people around me are too busy to cater to their plans to take over the world, who would care about a discolored, bottom of the class chamar boy? Hey, my answer is the same as you, hence the going out in brotherly glory plan.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I am happy at the prospect of never going back to the college again, forced to communicate with those judgmental pricks of classmates, teachers who would congratulate me and suggest that i would get a fat &lt;em&gt;sarkari&lt;/em&gt; job now. Somehow Infy, TCS, Polaris etc are never discussed with me.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Mom and Dad left for their monthly date, sister is out doing whatever she does. I am up, go to the computer room and dial up the Internet. Checking mail, yeah....no prospects, the self destruct plan stands. Phone rings.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I hate phone....she never calls, and she wont. She knows now, atleast suspects it...me being a chamaar. How can the shiniest, most popular girl date a chamar? Anyways, I will explain the situation later.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I answer, the digits seem similar - the call is from our family cell phone. I pick up, though i do not recognize the voice. The voice is of my uncle, he is trying to tell me something important in a very non important way. The car has broken down, and i need to come to get it fixed. I should get a friend to drive my bike back so I could drive the car after getting it repaired. The location is near a hospital. I say yes, and did not argue how illogical the plan sounded. In the background i could hear a lot of commotion. Anyways, i needed to patch up my appearance and drive a bike with no rear brakes for 100 kms. When you are on a death wish, these choices are really not a choice.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I call up a friend, a fellow SC/ST boy who flunked and now is a junior. Caste seems to be the only quality which defines my life right now. I am afraid of the general friends - ex girl friend might have blabbered..the news might have spread....and i have lost my looks. Most of people avoid me in college, the friends i thought i had left me because a girl who seems to have loved me, told everyone that i molested her. I never did. I literally and figuratively had lost my face and most friends with it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;SC friend shows up. He is riding pillion and i am driving my Bajaj caliber chroma. My friend is asking a lot of questions, i dont have any answers.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I drive, having some non-sense chatter with friend. My mind is racing though. Maybe my grandmother is sick or died and maybe my dad is too broken up to drive. This seemed to be the most logical interpretations of the facts i could recall.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;After an hours drive, we arrive at a hospital. As i enter, I could see 100s of faces I had forgotten. They seemed to be all watching me closely. I am not sure if its due to my current appearance or due to the incident.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Something is amiss. The damm car seems fine. People are crying, I am trying to find someone talk-able. Someone directs me to a sub group. Mother is crying, trying to be sad than she is.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Father is dead.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;How, why and what the fuck? Did her stupidity killed him or was it an assault? I am enraged, hoping it was an assault....and i get to kill someone for it...finally justify my existence. It was a heart attack.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I dont understand...are they sure? This is a good private hospital...they must be sure. I could have reacted way more naturally had I was not surrounded by literally 100s of people. Indians love drama, and i was customary bound to provide it today.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Something has hardened me enough to disobey conventions, and to realize what it means.....I am no longer the kid brother, or someone who can ask for help. With my stupid mom and uncontrollable sister.....what the literal fuck?? I need help to come to terms of what is happening to me and now this added responsibility too?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Nothing is fair. As my brain is processing the implications, I am interrupted - there are choices to be made. Where to do the &lt;em&gt;kriyas&lt;/em&gt;? I dont know. I am thinking here. I have my uncles, and I do not know what is to be done. My mother interferes. She turns off her crying for a moment and tells me to tell them Rohini, at our new home. I want to protest, but then a dollop of emotional superiority infused cold logic shrewd logic is disclosed....we need to keep up the reputation. I just want to be alone, as soon as possible. I say yes. Handing over the keys of the bike to the friend i tell him to be careful, the rear brakes are not working, the front ones do, but they are more effective than one anticipates.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Life would never be the same again.&lt;/p&gt;</content><category term="misc"></category></entry><entry><title>Why now ??</title><link href="https://chamarboy.com/why-now.html" rel="alternate"></link><published>2021-03-05T15:44:26+05:30</published><updated>2021-03-05T15:44:26+05:30</updated><author><name>Chamar Boy</name></author><id>tag:chamarboy.com,2021-03-05:/why-now.html</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;Date: 2020-09-26 22:57
Category: Story
Tags:  Why now, What, Caste, India&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I did not knew that the issue of caste discrimination is widespread in the world, let alone India.
Recently an ignorant asshole of general garbage origin shared an article which kind of forced me to increase the priority …&lt;/p&gt;</summary><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Date: 2020-09-26 22:57
Category: Story
Tags:  Why now, What, Caste, India&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I did not knew that the issue of caste discrimination is widespread in the world, let alone India.
Recently an ignorant asshole of general garbage origin shared an article which kind of forced me to increase the priority of this rather dead blog.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.zdnet.com/article/commentary-how-indias-ancient-caste-system-is-ruining-lives-in-silicon-valley/"&gt;Commentary: How India's ancient caste system is ruining lives in Silicon Valley&lt;/a&gt;  &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.washingtonpost.com/opinions/2020/07/13/new-lawsuit-shines-light-caste-discrimination-us-around-world/"&gt;WashingtonPost : A new lawsuit shines a light on caste discrimination in the U.S. and around the world&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://thewire.in/caste/cisco-caste-discrimination-silicon-valley-dalit-prejudice"&gt;The Cisco Case Could Expose Rampant Prejudice Against Dalits in Silicon Valley&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For the uninitiated, &lt;strong&gt;Chamar&lt;/strong&gt; is one of the sub castes, which also comes under rather lager or politically correct term &lt;strong&gt;Dalit&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Though centuries have passed, the discrimination remains solid as ever.
Most people generally assume that people belonging to this category of caste have an easy, express path to professional success and prosperity, A notion which i aim to challenge and provide a real life view.  &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I can only cover the aspects which i have faced in the most objective manner, to provide an unbiased perspective.&lt;/p&gt;</content><category term="misc"></category></entry><entry><title>A letter to P2</title><link href="https://chamarboy.com/a-letter-to-p2.html" rel="alternate"></link><published>2021-03-05T15:40:23+05:30</published><updated>2021-03-05T15:40:23+05:30</updated><author><name>Chamar Boy</name></author><id>tag:chamarboy.com,2021-03-05:/a-letter-to-p2.html</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;A letter to P2&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I loved you. Something in me still loves and misses you.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;My long due closure.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;P2 of all the females i have known in my life, you were the most kind, affectionate, intelligent and million other good things. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You were flawless. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I really wanted to be …&lt;/p&gt;</summary><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;A letter to P2&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I loved you. Something in me still loves and misses you.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;My long due closure.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;P2 of all the females i have known in my life, you were the most kind, affectionate, intelligent and million other good things. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You were flawless. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I really wanted to be good for you....for the fact that i could not imagine not having your voice in my life.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As you had given hundreds of hours of me whining about my ex girlfriend p1, I wanted to be sure.
For me, you were pure....an angel....maybe a god.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I really wanted to be sure, when i commit to you I commit for good, not as a insecure rebound from p1.......you were the nicest.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;And that time never arrived, and i was sure that it may never. I have not ever really gotten over p1...and i really knew that you have bigger things in store for you....to me it seemed like you chose to score low....your potential was infinite....and I am a chamar boy ....getting Rs 20 a week, who just wanted to die.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;And it got worse....skin gave away....and so did my belief of me being destined for self destruction.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I did misbehave with you and probably cheated you emotionally.....but you have to understand....you were the only good in my life back then.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I never really blamed for what happened next...i knew i deserved it....but i would have heard it from you.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It may be possible yet improbable that you might carry some guilt of what happened. Hope this helps....i deserved it and i am sorry.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I still miss you....for you are the only person who may still understand me.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For me, you are still the only person who is truly broken me.....it feels like you still have a part of me, and i still have yours. I still feel you...i still understand your emotions your hands your breath and those thousand different emotions your beautiful eyes conveyed.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I still imagine me exhaling on you soft skin and feeling your scent.&lt;/p&gt;</content><category term="misc"></category></entry></feed>