<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>Chamar Boy - misc</title><link href="https://chamarboy.com/" rel="alternate"></link><link href="https://chamarboy.com/feeds/misc.atom.xml" rel="self"></link><id>https://chamarboy.com/</id><updated>2021-03-07T02:04:10+05:30</updated><subtitle>An insight into SC/ST life</subtitle><entry><title>A letter to Anusha</title><link href="https://chamarboy.com/a-letter-to-anusha.html" rel="alternate"></link><published>2021-03-07T02:04:10+05:30</published><updated>2021-03-07T02:04:10+05:30</updated><author><name>Chamar Boy</name></author><id>tag:chamarboy.com,2021-03-07:/a-letter-to-anusha.html</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;Date: 2020-09-01 22:57
Category: Story
Tags: Anusha, College, Now, Missing you, India&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A letter to Anusha&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I loved you. Something in me still loves and misses you.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;My long due closure.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Anusha, of all the females i have known in my life, you were the most kind, affectionate, intelligent …&lt;/p&gt;</summary><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Date: 2020-09-01 22:57
Category: Story
Tags: Anusha, College, Now, Missing you, India&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A letter to Anusha&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I loved you. Something in me still loves and misses you.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;My long due closure.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Anusha, of all the females i have known in my life, you were the most kind, affectionate, intelligent and million other good things.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You were flawless.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I really wanted to be good for you....for the fact that i could not imagine not having your voice in my life.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As you had given hundreds of hours of me whining about my ex girlfriend Gunjan, I wanted to be sure.
For me, you were pure....an angel....maybe a god.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I really wanted to be sure, when i commit to you I commit for good, not as a insecure rebound from Gunjan.......you were the nicest.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;And that time never arrived, and i was sure that it may never. I have not ever really gotten over Gunjan...and i really knew that you have bigger things in store for you....to me it seemed like you chose to score low....your potential was infinite....and I am a chamar boy ....getting Rs 20 a week, who just wanted to die.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;And it got worse....skin gave away....and so did my belief of me being destined for self destruction.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I did misbehave with you and probably cheated you emotionally.....but you have to understand....you were the only good in my life back then.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I never really blamed for what happened next...i knew i deserved it....but i would have heard it from you.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It may be possible yet improbable that you might carry some guilt of what happened. Hope this helps....i deserved it and i am sorry.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I still miss you....for you are the only person who may still understand me.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For me, you are still the only person who is truly broken me.....it feels like you still have a part of me, and i still have yours. I still feel you...i still understand your emotions your hands your breath and those thousand different emotions your beautiful eyes conveyed.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I still imagine me exhaling on you soft skin and feeling your scent.&lt;/p&gt;</content><category term="misc"></category></entry></feed>