<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>Chamar Boy - Story</title><link href="https://chamarboy.com/" rel="alternate"></link><link href="https://chamarboy.com/feeds/story.atom.xml" rel="self"></link><id>https://chamarboy.com/</id><updated>2020-09-04T05:09:05+05:30</updated><subtitle>An insight into SC/ST life</subtitle><entry><title>Introduction</title><link href="https://chamarboy.com/introduction.html" rel="alternate"></link><published>2020-09-01T22:57:00+05:30</published><updated>2020-09-04T05:09:05+05:30</updated><author><name>Chamar Boy</name></author><id>tag:chamarboy.com,2020-09-01:/introduction.html</id><summary type="html">&lt;h1&gt;Who&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I am a Chamar boy, born in a somewhat normal middle class (not &lt;em&gt;Chamar
middle class, normal middle class&lt;/em&gt;) family.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;My father had a Bajaj super in 1990, and we got a telephone in 1997.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I was born in 1982 in a semi-urban village in Delhi.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I know its …&lt;/p&gt;</summary><content type="html">&lt;h1&gt;Who&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I am a Chamar boy, born in a somewhat normal middle class (not &lt;em&gt;Chamar
middle class, normal middle class&lt;/em&gt;) family.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;My father had a Bajaj super in 1990, and we got a telephone in 1997.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I was born in 1982 in a semi-urban village in Delhi.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I know its hard to imagine a 'village" in Delhi now, but in 1990 till
the time we stayed there, it had a well, we had cows and cow dung was
the primary fuel though my father got us LPG ever since i can remember.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So now here we are. Year is 2020, chaos year of my generation, but
somehow i am better placed then i ever was.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I have a spacious (in most senses) house, 2 cars, 2 dogs, a beautiful
and intelligent son and mostly loving wife.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;And I work at Facebook.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;That is the big reveal. 2cr.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;That declaration is not an achievement, I just want my readers to know
what they have here. I am just getting started, and I have a long way to
go.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This Facebook thing is important to me at-least as ever since i have
realized what Chamar is, and how apparently things have being laid out
for us - in sarkari sphere.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1&gt;WHY&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As I am getting older, I do tend to think about the past, mostly to
learn from it. I remember those days, when my self worth was negative
million.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I was targeted, gas lit at college, did not take it well, slipped in a
depression, developed psiorisis, spent years in an sham ayurvedic ashram
with skin swollen like a balloon filled with pus, abandonment by the
girl I loved, the girl who loved me, friends, my own family, failed
suicide attempt, living thru vengeance, death of father, a sister which
destroyed the family, destroyed my existence to grab hers.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;All because I am a Chamar.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It was not all bad, I somehow realized strengths which I thought I never
had, and did generally well. Something kept me pushing, and I kept
breathing.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I want to share my journey with you, so anyone who feels like i did in
my Chamar years can get some semblance of hope or direction and
hopefully he/she does not commit the grave mistakes I did, or felt like
how I felt.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;To Readers:&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I hope you get a balanced view of a Chamar life and hopefully next time
you feel like feeling taller, maybe you will spare the the sc/st clan in
your class, office or school. And you have the full freedom to give me a
piece of your mind, absolutely brutally.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I have designed the blog in a way that anonymous are welcome and give me
their best shot. Its sort of a fuel to me now.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;To my fellow chamaar/sc/st readers&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I hope you learn.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I hope you feel hopeful.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I hope you can believe in yourself, than what you classmates are telling
you silently.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I hope if my journey can benefit any 1 of you, my efforts would make
sense to me.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1&gt;HOW&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I will try to narrate it in a novel kinda style. You already know where
I am. Logically my story starts in class 11, when I started realizing
the implications of being a chamaar meant, for career, for being friends
with girls and home.&lt;/p&gt;</content><category term="Story"></category><category term="Introduction"></category><category term="Start"></category><category term="Why"></category><category term="What"></category></entry></feed>