<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>ChamarBoy - An insight into SC/ST life. - Story</title><link href="http://chamarboy.com/" rel="alternate"></link><link href="http://chamarboy.com/feeds/story.atom.xml" rel="self"></link><id>http://chamarboy.com/</id><updated>2020-09-01T22:57:00+05:30</updated><entry><title>Introduction</title><link href="http://chamarboy.com/introduction.html" rel="alternate"></link><published>2020-09-01T22:57:00+05:30</published><updated>2020-09-01T22:57:00+05:30</updated><author><name>Chamar Boy</name></author><id>tag:chamarboy.com,2020-09-01:/introduction.html</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;I am a chamar boy, born in a somewhat normal middle class (not chamar middle class, normal middle class) family&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;My father had a Bajaj super in 1990, and we got a telephone in 1997.
I was born in 1982 in a semi-urban village in Delhi. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I know its hard …&lt;/p&gt;</summary><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;I am a chamar boy, born in a somewhat normal middle class (not chamar middle class, normal middle class) family&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;My father had a Bajaj super in 1990, and we got a telephone in 1997.
I was born in 1982 in a semi-urban village in Delhi. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I know its hard to imagine a 'village" in Delhi now, but in 1990 till the time we stayed there, it had a well, we had cows and cow dung was the primary fuel though my father got us LPG ever since i can remember.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So now here we are. Year is 2020, chaos year of my generation, but somehow i am better placed then i ever was. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I have a spacious (in most senses) house, 2 cars, 2 dogs, a beautiful and intelligent son and mostly loving wife.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;And I work at Facebook.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;That is the big reveal. 2cr. I want to share my journey with you, so anyone who feels like i did in my chamar years can get some semblance of hope or direction.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This Facebook thing is important to me atleast as ever since i have realized what chamar is, and how apparently things have being laid out for us - in sarkari sphere. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It is a deal with devil and living a life where you never knew what your worth was or taking a chance on yourself.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I hope you get a balanced view of a chamar life and hopefully give me a piece of your mind, absolutely brutally. I have designed the blog in a way that anonymous are welcome and give me their best shot. You have powered me, and would continue to provide me more ammo to succeed.
And to my fellow chamaar/sc/st boys and gals....I hope you benefit. I hope if my journey can benefit any 1 of you, my efforts would make sense to me.&lt;/p&gt;</content><category term="Story"></category></entry></feed>